nobullying.com 2018-05-06

# Privacy Policy - NoBullying - Bullying & CyberBullying ResourcesNoBullying – Bullying & CyberBullying Resources

NoBullying.com cares about your personal information and we take your privacy very seriously. By using NoBullying.com you agree to the following Privacy Policy. This policy covers the treatment of personal information that NoBullying.com collects when you are using the [NoBullying.com](https://nobullying.com/) website. This policy does not apply to practices of third parties that NoBullying.com has no control over.

NoBullying.com (“we”, “us”, “website”, “our” and “site”) is a trade mark owned by No More Bullying Ltd.

This document relates to all services available through the domain www.NoBullying.com. and its subdomains and any officially linked social media support service, including but not limited to Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, and YouTube.

The terms (“Client(s)”, “user(s)” “you”, “your” and “Service Provider”) when used in these Terms mean any user of this website offering, providing, availing of service(s) or seeking to receive or provide service(s), also users participating in the NoBullying.com Referral Program. These users can be registered or non-registered.

BY PROVIDING PERSONAL DATA TO US AND/OR BY USING NOBULLYING.COM YOU GIVE YOUR CONSENT THAT ALL PERSONAL DATA THAT YOU SUBMIT MAY BE PROCESSED IN THE MANNER AND FOR THE PURPOSES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT. NOBULLYING.COM RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CHANGE THIS POLICY AND WILL PROVIDE NOTIFICATION OF ANY CHANGES ON THE WEBSITE ITSELF. HENCE YOU ARE REQUIRED TO RECHECK IT REGULARLY.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS POLICY, DO NOT USE THE NoBullying.com WEBSITE.

**INTRODUCTION**

NoBullying.com is an online website that allows users learn more and contribute to fighting bullying in all its shapes and forms. Please be aware that any comment, review, profile, video, picture or any other content added to NoBullying.com website is provided by you on a non-proprietary and non-confidential basis. When providing personal information to NoBullying.com you are voluntarily and expressly agreeing to accept the Terms and Conditions of this Privacy Policy along with the standard website Terms and Conditions.

NoBullying.com uses search facilities across the website. Information you have provided in your profile, including but not limited to any content you have added to the site will be used to populate this search engine.

**AUTOMATIC INFORMATION**

We receive automatic information through NoBullying.com.com and its authorised agents when you use the website. We automatically receive and record certain ‘traffic data’, including your IP address, cookie information and page views. We use this information to identify problems with the website and offer you a better service. The IP address shall only be analysed in case of attack on NoBullying.com’s system and for website statistics.

We use all information we gather to offer you a personalized website experience, to create personalized web pages and offer a better service to users.

We use Hyperlinks to link from one page on the website to another relevant page on the website. We may use technology to track how often these links are used and which pages are viewed. This technology does not identify you personally but provides statistics for the website, so we can improve our service.

We apply appropriate technical and organisational security measures in order to protect your personal data against unauthorised access, part or full loss or manipulation.

**USE OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

We will use your personal information to provide you with a personalized experience each visit to the website.

NoBullying.com employees and third party agents may have some access to personal information on NoBullying.com that is necessary during the normal course of business.

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transfers, user information is usually the type of information that is transferred. In the case of a merger, acquisition, reorganisation, sale of assets or bankruptcy assets such as user data may be transferred to a third party successor. We do not sell or rent personal information to third parties without your consent.

We will release personal information if necessary to comply with a legal request.

NoBullying.com allows for RSS syndication of its public content from NoBullying.com.

From time to time, NoBullying.com may take part in surveys or polls. You may be asked to provide personal information or permit the transfer of such information as part of the terms of the survey or poll. It will be disclosed at the point of collecting if it is NoBullying.com collecting this information or a third party.

We will send you services or promotional communications through email and notices on the website – which you can opt out of.

We will use information gathered from the website when working with our partners to offer you on site advertising that is relevant to you.

We will use your personal information if a dispute arises and we need to contact you in an attempt to resolve this dispute.

Except in the cases above – we will contact you when your personal information may be shared with a third party, where you will have the option to opt out of such sharing.

**COOKIES AND THEIR USE**

We use Cookies to gather non personal information about your visits to our website. However, you may turn off these cookies as most of the browsers allow you to do so. If you want to know how to do this, go to your help menu on your browser. However, if you choose not to accept cookies, your user experience on our site may be affected. We use cookies to:

  * estimate our audience size and usage pattern.
  * store information about your preferences so we can customise our site according to your individual interests.
  * speed up your searches.

**WHAT ARE COOKIES?**

Cookies are alphanumeric information files which your browser automatically saves to the hard drive of your computer when you visit a website. Having active cookies allows for quick login every time you visit the website. Using cookies does not mean that we receive new personal data about you as a visitor to our website. Data collected using cookies is statistical in nature and indicates a user’s browsing actions and patterns. It does not identify any individual. To remove the cookies at any point from your computer, you can delete them using your browser.

NoBullying.com may also use from time to time a technology that is embedded into web pages or in email that allows the website to track page views. Unlike cookies these are not stored on your hard drive. This technology is often called Clear GIF’s or Web Beacons this technology does not personally identify you.

**YOUR ACTIONS ON NOBULLYING.COM**

When you complete your profile, you may choose whether to provide or not to provide your contact details or other personal information on this public website. Our advice is that you do not provide this information on your public profile to avoid it being used by any third parties that may result in unsolicited emails or communications. DO NOT POST INFORMATION ON NOBULLYING.COM THAT YOU WANT TO KEEP PRIVATE AS NOBULLYING.COM IS AN OPEN WEBSITE.

NoBullying.com operates an invite service throughout its website, where you have the option to use this invite system or not, to invite or tell your friends/connections about the website or content on the website. While doing so some part of your information may be available for such person to see and identify you.

When you write a comment, post and/or review, you will be identified by your full name and picture, information which is available from your profile. Your public profile, once confirmed by you will be shown and available to all users of NoBullying.com to view.

You may use a link on NoBullying.com to visit another website, as per standard Terms and Conditions, however, NoBullying.com does not endorse any other website with or without links to its own website. If you visit another website you should review their standard Terms and Conditions and Privacy policy as it may differ from NoBullying.com. We do not control the policies of other websites.

**FINANCIAL INFORMATION**

Any financial information you send through the website such as credit card details, will be passed through our secure gateway which we operate in conjunction with our specialist payment service. We do not collect any card payment data, nor do we share this information with any third party – any payments are processed directly between you and the payment service – facilitated by the NoBullying.com website. In case you use a corporate credit card, your billing information may be shared with your employer.

**GENERAL**

Do not abuse NoBullying.com or its users by using spam, abuse or other ways and means to violate this policy.

Personal Information that is provided to NoBullying.com will be secured in accordance with industry standards and technology. The internet is not 100% secure, we cannot ensure the security of any information transmitted to NoBullying.com. There is no guarantee that the information will not be accessed, copied or used for purposes that were not originally agreed to. You are responsible for maintaining the secure access to your account through your password and/or social login

We do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under 18 years of age. As a parent or legal guardian, please do not allow your children to submit personal information without your permission.

**COMMUNICATION**

NoBullying.com will send you welcome or confirmation emails when you first register to the website. To get these emails you need to ‘opt in’. You will be asked to confirm which if any newsletters you wish to receive and to confirm your email address. You may change your subscription at any time – each email contains an unsubscribe button.

We will never provide your email address to a third party without your permission. The newsletters available from NoBullying.com may include related news, products or service information, promotions, surveys, article posts, or other topics that we deem may be of interest.

You may also be notified by email of messages or requests from NoBullying.com – contacts from possible customers or friend requests. Again you can opt out of any of these emails by using the unsubscribe button in each email or via your profile settings.

Please do note that you may continue to receive any important or urgent emails regarding changes or updates to NoBullying.com’s Terms and Conditions or Privacy policy.

**PROTECTING PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We take precautions, including administrative, technical and physical measures to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. However, unfortunately no security system or system of transmitting data over the Internet can be guaranteed to be entirely secure. You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. For your own privacy protection we advise you not to include sensitive personal information in any emails you may send to us. Please do not send credit card numbers or any sensitive personal information to us via email.

**RETAINING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

At www.NoBullying.com we retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfil the purposes outlined in this policy document, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted/mandated by applicable law.

**INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTY**

Any third party including but not limited to users, service provider, advertiser or service seeker is not endorsed by NoBullying.com and it shall in no case be deemed so. Any information provided to any third party is your own and sole decision and we are not responsible in case any such information provided by you to third party is misused by the third party.

**TRANSFER OF DATA ABROAD**

Please note we may keep your personal information between our offices and third party partner servers which may be located globally. Where your personal data is transferred to a country outside of the European Economic Area, we will ensure the guardians of this date keep it confidential and in full accordance with applicable data laws.

BY REGISTERING WITH NOBULLYING.COM YOU ARE CONFIRMING THAT YOU HAVE READ AND AGREED TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND AGREE TO ALL POINTS HELD WITHIN, INCLUDING TRANSFER OF DATA ABROAD.

**CHANGE IN PRIVACY POLICY**

NoBullying.com may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time as and when required without prior notice, at its sole discretion. However, any such modification / change will be amended in the Privacy Policy on the website hence we advise you to recheck it every time you visit our website or share any information on it as it may not be practically possible for us to inform each and every individual about such change for reason of non-availability of email address or inactive email id or for any other technical or non-technical reason.

**PHISHING**

Identity theft or “phishing” are becoming common fraud practices. NoBullying.com will never ask you in email or through any other communication method for your credit card information, account username, login password, or any other sensitive information.

**GOVERNING LAW**

This Privacy Statement forms part of our website Terms and Conditions of business and the substantive laws of Northern Ireland govern any claim of whatever nature arising out of or relating to the use of this website. All actions or proceedings arising out of or relating to this Privacy Statement, its validity, performance, enforcement or breach, or the subject matter of this Privacy Statement may be heard in the courts of Northern Ireland and you consent and submit yourself to the personal jurisdiction of Northern Irish courts for all such purposes. We retain the right to bring legal proceedings in any jurisdiction where we believe that breach of this agreement is taking place or originating.

**TESTIMONIALS**

With your consent we may post your stories, experiences or insights on the website anonymously.

**CONTACT US**

If at any time you would like to contact us with your views about our privacy practices, or with any inquiry relating to your personal information, you can do so by sending an e-mail to us at support@NoBullying.com. Or you can fill in this [contact form here.](https://nobullying.com/contact-us/)

Read more about the[ Terms of using NoBullying here.](https://nobullying.com/terms-and-conditions/)
